gloworld.com 2009-11-01

# Glo World

|   
  
  |  |     
---  
| GLOBACOM PRIVACY POLICY  
---  
_Last Updated: October 22nd, 2005._

Globacom Nigeria Limited respects the privacy of all of its users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains Globacom Nigeria Limited's ("Globacom") treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on or related to the Globacom website. This Privacy Policy also explains how you can ask questions and make suggestions about our privacy practices and review and update your personal information.  
  
We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully and to check back periodically as this Privacy Policy may change form time to time. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies or websites which are not owned or controlled by Globacom  
| INFORMATION COLLECTED  
---  
In the course of operating the Globacom Services, we may collect two types of information about our users: **Personal Information** and **Non-Personal Information**.   
  
**Personal Information** is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, birth date and gender. Personal Information is collected by us when you choose to provide it to us when registering for a Globacom Service, such as when you choose to subscribe to a Globacom Service, enter a Globacom promotion or choose to receive a Globacom newsletter. In addition, if you choose to contact any of our customer service representatives, we may keep a record of that correspondence so that we may fully address the subject matter. We may also receive Personal Information from our business partners and other third parties, provided that such third parties confirm to us that you have permitted them to share such information. 

Business contact information such as the name, title, business address, email address or telephone number of a business or professional person or an employee of an organization is not considered Personal Information.  
  
**Non-Personal Information** is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address), the domain used to access a Globacom Service, and the type and version of browser or operating system being used. Aggregate information, such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors and average time spent on a Globacom Service, is also considered Non-Personal Information.

**Non-Personal Information** is collected or derived by us in the course of operating the Globacom Services. For example, our Web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information which is provided through your browser or stored on a Cookie or through a Web Beacon when you choose to visit a Globacom Service. Non-Personal Information is used by Globacom as described here.  
  
| USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION   
---  
Personal Information may be used by us for the following purposes:  
  
Providing you with the Globacom Services and information you have requested from us, including your use of the Globacom Site. We may from time to time use your Personal Information to contact you about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to the Globacom Services;   
If you indicated that you were interested in receiving offers or information from Globacom or certain of our selected sponsors or advertisers, Globacom or such sponsors or advertisers may send you email materials and other mailings about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. If at any time you would like to end your subscription to any such email materials, follow the directions posted at the bottom of the email material;  
  
If you enter a contest or other promotion offered on a Globacom Site, we may, under the rules of the promotion, use your name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion;   
  
Globacom may also use Personal Information if it has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful when investigating a contravention of any law or in order to protect or defend a legal interest.   
  
| DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION   
---  
  
We will not sell or rent your Personal Information to anyone. We will only disclose your Personal Information to third parties:  
  
Where you have specifically given us your consent to disclose your Personal Information for a designated purpose;   
  
Who are acting on our behalf as our agents, suppliers or service providers, solely to enable us to more efficiently provide you with the Globacom Services. Such entities act under strict contractual controls, requiring them to maintain the confidentiality of all such Personal Information and to use such information solely for purposes related to the provision of the Globacom Services;   
  
As may be set out in the Terms and Conditions applicable to a Globacom Service, to facilitate the provision of such Globacom Service, such as fulfilling legal requirements;   
  
As required by law, including by an order of any court, institution or body with jurisdiction or authority to compel the production of information, or in order to protect or defend a legal interest;   
  
In connection with a Globacom corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, or a sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of Globacom provided that the Personal Information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy by the entity acquiring the information.   
  
| LINKS TO OTHER SITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS  
---  
  
A Globacom Service may contain links to other websites and services. While we try to link only to sites and services that share our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that we are not responsible for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by, other companies or websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Globacom Services referencing this Privacy Policy.   
  
| SECURITY  
---  
  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us. Globacom takes technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect Personal Information that you provide to us. We instruct our employees with access to your Personal Information that it is to be used only in adherence with the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy and the laws applicable to each specific business.  
  
In certain areas, such as when you provide credit card information to us, we work to help protect the security of your credit card information.  
You can help protect the security of your Personal Information as well. For instance, never give out your password, since this is what is used to access your Account or Registration Information. Also remember to log out of your account and close your browser window when you finish using a Globacom Service or surfing the Web, so that other people using the same computer won't have access to your information.  
  
| CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY   
---  
  
Globacom may from time to time change its Privacy Policy as new Globacom Services are added or old ones changed. Changes will be effective when notice of such change is posted at the Globacom Site. Please check this Privacy Policy regularly for updates by checking the date of "Last Update" at the top of this document.   
  
| ADDITIONAL PRIVACY PROCEDURES   
---  
  
Privacy procedures specific to a Globacom Service may be found on the Globacom Site at the location of the particular Globacom Service, or in additional terms referenced at the Globacom Site. Those procedures are an addendum to this policy, and are provided to you at the place where they will be of most use and relevance to you.  
  
| QUESTIONS, COMMENTS OR SUGGESTIONS  
---  
  
If you have questions, comments or suggestions about this Privacy Policy or Globacom's privacy practices that were not answered here, send an e-mail to [webmaster@gloworld.com](mailto:webmaster@gloworld.com)  
  
Copyright 2005 Globacom Limited. All Rights Reserved.
